Office of the President Mary Maples Dunn Files, 1985-1995
Smith College Archives
- SERIES VI. ALUMNAE, (7 document boxes / 2.9 linear feet)
  Note: Boxes 2-5 of the Alumnae series is restricted until June 2005, because of its alphabetical rather than chronological arrangement.
  This series includes material on a number of issues related to the alumnae, as well as the Alumnae Association and its activities. The bulk of the files contain information about the Alumnae Association, class reunions, Smith Clubs, and specific individuals. The section related to individuals is in alphabetical order, and contains correspondence to, from and about alumnae. Many are routine and pro forma letters of thank you for attending certain functions, or congratulations on administrative successes. However, there are also letters scattered throughout addressing specific issues pertinent to the period. Information about alumnae involvement with Admissions can be found in the records of Alumnae/Admissions Task Force in the Committees and Boards series, and in the records of the Admissions Office's Candidates Committees in the Administrative Offices series.
  - Alumnae Association
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -General 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -General 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -General 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -General 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -Meeting Agendas 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Alumnae Biography Project 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - -Black Alumnae Weekend 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -College/Alumnae Task Force on Diversity (Box 1)
      See Series IX. Committees & Boards-College/Alumnae Task Force on Diversity
    - -Smith Alumnae Quarterly 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Travel/Tours 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -Young Alumnae Conference 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -Young Alumnae Survey 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alumnae Fund 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alumnae Fund 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alumnae Fund 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dining Consolidation, Alumnae correspondence regarding (Box 1)
  - Feminist & Lesbian Alumnae of Smith College [FLASC] (Box 1)
    See Series IV. Administrative Issues-Lesbianism-Feminist & Lesbian Alumnae of Smith College
  - Individuals
    - -A ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - -Ba ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - -Baldwin, Ainslie 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -Be-Bl ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -Bo ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - -Br-Bu ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - -Brayton, Charlotte 1985-1987, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - -Briggs, Lucy Barnard 1988-1995 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - -Brown, Elizabeth 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - -Brown, Locke 1987-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - -Burack, Sylvia 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - -Bush, Barbara 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        See also Series XI.Events-Opening Convocation (1989)
    - -Ca- Ch ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - -Carey, Ernestine Gilbreth 1988-1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - -Chapman, Dolly 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - -Ci-Cz ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - -D ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - -Denniston, Rosemary 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - -E ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - -Ericsson, Jane 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -F ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -G ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -Ha-He ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Hi-Hz ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -I-J ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -K ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - -Kahn, Louise 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -La-Le ca. 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - -L'Engle, Madeleine 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - -Landstrom, Elsie and Hyla Doc 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Li-Lz ca. 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -Ma-Me ca. 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - -McCallum, Taffy Gould 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -Mi-Mz ca. 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - -Milbank, Helen 1986-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - -Mitchell, Margaretta 1989-1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -N ca. 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -O ca. 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - -O'Brien, Margaret 1988-1995 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - -P-Q ca. 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - -Pyotte, Patty 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - -Ra-Ri ca. 1985-1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - -Rankin, Clara 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - -Reagan, Nancy 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - -Ro-Rz ca. 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - -Rosenfeld, Erika 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - -Sa-Sl ca. 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - -Slater, Elaine 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - -Sm-Sz ca. 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - -Smith, Bernadet Carey 1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - -Smith, Helen Bryan 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - -T ca. 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - -Tangeman, Clementine 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - -U-V ca. 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - -W ca. 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - -X-Z ca. 1985-1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - -Miscellaneous 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Ketcham Project 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mayoral Meeting 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Reunions
    - -1986 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - -1987 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - -1988 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - -1989 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - -1990 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -1991 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - - 1992
      - -General 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - -"Suddenly Single" Panel 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - -1993 1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Reunion Task Force 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Smith Clubs
    - -General 1985-1992, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - -California 1985-1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - -Delaware 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - -Florida 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - -Georgia 1986-1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -Illinois 1985-1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - -Massachusetts 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - -Minnesota 1985-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -Missouri 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - -New Hampshire 1985, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - -New York 1985-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - -North Carolina 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - -Pennsylvania 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - -Texas 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - -Washington, D.C./Baltimore 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - -Washington, D.C./Baltimore 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - -Canada 1985 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - -Europe 1987-1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Smith Voices 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- SERIES VII. BUILDINGS & GROUNDS, (2 document boxes / 0.8 linear feet)
  Student residences are grouped together and organized alphabetically.
  This series includes records related to the maintenance and development of campus structures and infrastructure. The largest construction projects during Dunn's term was the renovation of the Clark Science Center.
  Related material may be found in the Committees and Boards series in the records of the Campus Planning Committee, Facilities Planning Committee, Committee on Faculty Offices, Grounds Committee, Ad-hoc Committee for the Selection of Architects and Supervision of Building Programs, Committee on Space Allocation, and the Campus Beautification Committee. There is additional information in the Administrative Offices series in the records of the Physical Plant as well as the Assistant to the President for Campus Planning (President's Office).
  - General 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -Campus Signage 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -Handicap Accessibillity (Box 1)
      See Series V. Administrative Offices-Institutional Research for memo dated 4 Feb 1986 which lists buildings and accomodations -and- Series V. Administrative Offices-Special Needs Services
    - -Master Plan (Box 1)
      See Series IX. Cttees & Bds-Campus Committee -and- Series IX. Cttees & Bds-College Planning & Resources, Committee on
    - -Parking & Traffic 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -Parking & Traffic 1988-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Facilities
    - -General 1985-1986, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -Croquet Cart 1986, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Riding Facilities 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bass Hall (Box 1)
    See Series VII. Buildings & Grounds-Clark Science Center-Addition
  - Botanic Gardens
    - -Annual Reports 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -General 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -Landscape Architecture Symposium 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -President's Elm 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clark Science Center
    - -General 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -Addition
      - -General 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - -General 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - -Action Plan May 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - -Dedication 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - -Federal Funding 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - -Federal Funding 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - -Ground Breaking 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - -White Report 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Animal Care Facilities 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - College Hall 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dewey
    - -General 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Student Correspondence 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Fort Hill (Box 2)
    See Series II. Academic Depts.-Education & Child Study-Campus School
  - President's House 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Student Residences
    - -General 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - -Dining Consolidation (Box 2)
    - -Dawes House 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - -Duckett House 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - -Hopkins House 1992, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - -Hubbard House 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - -Sessions House 1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - -Talbot House (Box 2)
      See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Strategic Planning Committees-Dining, for Talbot alumnae corresponce re Dining Consolidation
    - -Washburn House 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - -Ziskind House 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- SERIES VIII. COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES, (2 document boxes / 0.8 linear feet)
  The files are organized alphabetically by institution, with a series of alphabetical miscellaneous material at the end.
  This series consists of correspondence, reports and newspaper clippings from other institutions regarding cooperative programs, institutional activities and events, as well as common educational issues.
  For institutions of either the Five Colleges, Seven Sisters or Twelve College Exchange, see also the Intercollegiate Associations series.
  - Amherst College 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Beloit College 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bentley College 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bowdoin College 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bryn Mawr College 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carleton College 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chatham College 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chicago, University of 1986-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Columbia University 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hampshire College 1985-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Macalester College 1986-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts, University of 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Massachusetts, University of 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mount Holyoke College
    - -General 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - -International Conference on Worldwide Education for Women 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Oberlin College
    - -General 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - -Future of Science Conference 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - -Future of Science Conference 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - -Research Grant Questionnaire 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Pennsylvania State University 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Swarthmore College 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Trinity College 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous
    - --A-D ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -E-M ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - -N-R ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -S-Z ca. 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Inauguration Invitations [Sample Only] 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- SERIES IX. COMMITTEES AND BOARDS, (9 document boxes / 3.8 linear feet)
  This series includes correspondence, reports and working papers of the standing and ad-hoc committees and boards of the college. The most central and far-reaching decision-making bodies are the Board of Trustees, the Board of Counselors, and the Committee on Planning and Resources (previously the College Planning Committee and the Faculty Planning Committee). However, college policy and the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act require the restriction of the records of both the Board of Trustees and the Board of Counselors. Other significant committees in this series include several faculty committees, the Committee on Social Responsibility and the Committee on Student Affairs. Also included in this series are three free-standing administrative groups: Administrative Department Heads, Senior Administrative Group, and Senior Staff. The files of the Senior Staff are the most extensive of these three groups. The Senior Staff (also know as the President's Staff) included key administrative figures, such as the Treasurer, the Directors of Development and Public Relations, Assistants to the President, and Deans and Associate Deans. Minutes and major reports from most committees are available in the Dean of the Faculty Records of the Smith College Archives.
  - General
    - -Appointment Letters 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - -Appointment Letters 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - -Appointment Letters 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - -Appointment Letters 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - -Appointment Letters 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - -Lists 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - -Miscellaneous and Proposed Committees 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic Policy, Committee On 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ACRA (Box 1)
    See Series IX. Cttees & Bds-Resource Allocation, Advisory Committee on
  - Administrative Board 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Admission, Board of 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Admission, Board of 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Admission, Board of 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Advancement Committee 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Committees 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Committees 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Committees 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alumnae Relations & Support, Joint Commission on
    - -General 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -General 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -General undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -1990 Report May 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Prog and Exercise & Sport Studies, Cttee to Review the Structure 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Athletics, Committee on 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Benefits Advisory Committee 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Budget Officers 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Budget Officers 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Budget Officers 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Budget Officers 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Business Staff Directors 1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Campus Committee 1985-1988, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Campus Planning, Faculty Advisory Committee on 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Civil Rights Board 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - College Planning & Resources
    - -General 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - -General 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - -General 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -General 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -General 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -Child Care 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -Master Plan (Box 4)
      See also Series IX. Committees & Boards-Campus Committee
    - -Planning Task Force 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - -Strategic Planning (Box 4)
      See Series IX. Cttees & Bds-Strategic Planning Cttees
  - Community Policy, Committee on (Box 4)
    - -General 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -General 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - -Equal Opportunity Employment (Box 4)
      See Series XII. Faculty & Staff-Equal Opportunity Employment and Grievance Procedures
    - -Ombuds Person Office Proposal 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - -Otelia Cromwell Day, Subttee on (Box 4)
      See Series XI. Events-O. Cromwell Day
    - -Race/Diversity 1987-1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - -Smith Design for Institutional Diversity (Box 4)
      See Series IV. Administrative Issues-Diversity-Smith Design
    - -Task Force on South Africa 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Diversity, College/Alumnae Task Force on 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Enrollment Management Committee 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Enrollment Management Committee Feb-Mar 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Enrollment Management Committee Apr-Oct 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Enrollment Management Committee Nov 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Facilities Use Committee 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Appointments, Advisory Committee on 1989-1990, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Compensation and Development, Committee on 1986, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Future of the College, Ad hoc Committee on- (Box 5)
    See Series IX. Committees & Boards-Strategic Planning Committees
  - Honorary Degrees, Committee on 1986-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Marshals Committee 1986, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Medical Benefits Review Committee 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Motion Picture Committee 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Personnel Policy Board
    - -General 1986-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - -Classification & Compensation Plan Meeting 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Planning Task Force (Box 5)
    See Series IX. Committees & Boards-College Planning and Resources-Planning Task Force
  - Pre-Health Advisors, Board of 1985-1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Search Committee 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - President's Staff (Box 5)
    See Series IX. Committees & Boards-Senior Staff
  - Radiation Safety Committee 1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Registration & Standardization of Institutional Data, Committee for 1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Resource Allocation, Advisory Committee on 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Resource Coordinating Committee 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Resource Coordinating Committee 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Science Planning Committee 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Senior Staff
    - -General 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - -General 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - -General 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - -General 1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - -General 1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - -General 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - -General 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - -General 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - -General 1994 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - -General 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - -Retreat (Box 7)
      - -1988 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - -1989 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - -1990 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - -1991 1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Smith Management Program Advisory Committee 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Space Allocation Committee
    - -General 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - -General 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - -General 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - -Student Cultural Organization Space 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - -Utilization Study 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Special Needs Advisory Committee 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Staff Conference (Box 7)
  - Staff Council
    - -General 1991 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - -General 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - -Task Force Information Packet 1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Strategic Planning Committees
    - -General 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - -General 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - -George Kaludis Associates Oct-Jun 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - -George Kaludis Associates Jul-Dec 1990 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - -Administration & Infrastructure 1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - -Campus School & Child Care
      - -General 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - -Correspondence with MMD Response 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - -Alumnae Correspondence 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - -Parent Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - -Miscellaneous Correspondence 1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - -Dining
      - -General 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - -Alumnae Correspondence with MMD Response 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - -Alumnae Correspondence without MMD Response 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - -Student & Parent Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - -Educational Experience 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - -Faculty & Academic Support 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - -Infirmary Care 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - -Student Employment 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - -Student Population 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - -Voluntary Separation Packages (Box 9)
      See Series IX. Cttees & Bds-Transition, Advisory Cttee on -and- Resource Allocation, Advisory Cttee on
  - Student Life Committee 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Study Abroad, Committee on 1985-1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Summer Programs, Task Force on 1985-1986, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Tenure & Promotion, Committee on 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - TIAA-CREF Retirement Plan Review Committee 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Transition, Advisory Committee on-General 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- SERIES X. ENGAGEMENTS, (5 document boxes / 2.1 linear feet)
  This series of records works in concert with the Speeches and Events series to provide a detailed description of the activities and responsibilities of the President of Smith College. Included are a set of files containing details of various off-campus appointments and events the president attended (organized by date of event or appointment). There are also a set of calendars, daily schedules, travel schedules, and a sample of engagements the president had to refuse. Note: Frances Volkman was acting president for the spring semester of 1991.
  - October 1985-Macalester College 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - February 1987-Marietta College 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - June 1987-Williston Northampton School 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - June 1989-Connecticut River Excursion 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - February 1993-National Association of Principals of Schools for Girls 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - June 1993-Dwight-Englewood School 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Calendars
    - -1985 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - -1986 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - -1987 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - -1988 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - -1989 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - -1990 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - -1991 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - -Frances Volkman 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - -1992 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - -1993 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - -1994 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Conferences 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Daily Schedules
    - -Mar-Aug 1985 Mar-Aug 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - -Sep-Dec 1985 Sep-Dec 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - -Jan-May 1986 Jan-May 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - -Jun-Oct 1986 Jun-Oct 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - -Nov-Dec 1986 Nov-Dec 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - -Jan-Apr 1987 Jan-Apr 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - -May-Aug 1987 May-Aug 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - -Sep-Dec 1987 Sep-Dec 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - -Jan-Apr 1988 Jan-Apr 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - -May-Aug 1988 May-Aug 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - -Sep-Dec 1988 Sep-Dec 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - -Jan-Mar 1989 Jan-Mar 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - -Apr-Jun 1989 Apr-Jun 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - -Jul-Sep 1989 Jul-Sep 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - -Oct-Dec 1989 Oct-Dec 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - -Jan-Apr 1990 Jan-Apr 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - -May-Aug 1990 May-Aug 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - -Sep-Dec 1990 Sep-Dec 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - -Jan-Aug 1991 Jan-Aug 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - -Jan-Aug 1991-Frances Volkman Jan-Aug 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - -Sep-Dec 1991 Sep-Dec 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - -Jan-Jun 1992 Jan-Jun 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - -Jul-Dec 1992 Jul-Dec 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - -Jan-Apr 1993 Jan-Apr 1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - -Apr-Jul 1993 Apr-Jul 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)